

Contact Me

- 08169039269
- e ukwuomatochi112@gma il.com
- https://github.com/Tochy112

Social Profile

- linkedin.com/in/ukwuo ma-tochukwu-052462223
- witter.com/tochy112

Other Info

Skills

HTML5, CSS3, ES6, JQUERY, BOOTSTRAP, REACT, PHP, MySQL, Git.

Languages English

UKWUOMA TOCHUKWU

Frontend Developer



About Me

I'm a frontend web developer with experience in designing and developing interfaces using fronted development tools.

I have basic experience in using a server-side language, PHP, and a database management system, MySQL.

I have experience working with various teams during various internships I participated in, using Github as a means for collaboration.

I'm a curious and fast learner with a problem-solving mind.



Experience

9/2021 -2/2022 Oluaka Institute Of Technology | Junior Frontend Developer

Worked as an intern in the institute.

4/2022 -5/2022 Side Hustle | React Developer

It was an internship experience. learned the basics of React.js during this period.



Education

Interest

Web development, Technical writing

2018 - 2022 Nnamdi Azikiwe University | BSc

Mathematics

I'm currently a final year student at Nnamdi Azikiwe University in the Department of Mathematics.

2011 - 2017 Holy Ghost College | SSCE

2005 - 2011 Police Primary School | First School Leaving



Projects

Side Hustle | Admin Dashboard

Designed and built an admin dashboard during my internship with Side Hustle using react.js

https://admin-21.netlify.app

Side Hustle | PiggyVest

Cloned the piggy vest website using react

https://campwork01piggyvestclone.netlify.app

Side Hustle | Todo App

Built the UI of a Todo application using react

https://week2-todo-api-app.vercel.app

Jackocoin | E-commerce

Built an e-commerce website.

https://fruitty.netlify.app